farminguk.com 2019-03-27

# Fair Processing Notice

**What we need**

Red Hen Promotions Ltd (on behalf of FarmingUK) will be what’s known as the ‘Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information. This does however include name, address, email etc.

**Why we need it**

We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with our advertising services in line with the overall contract. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you.

**What we do with it**

All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the European Union. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so.

We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data.

**How long we keep it**

We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years after which time it will be destroyed. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. More information on our retention schedule can obtained by contacting our Data Protection Officer.

**What we would also like to do with it**

We would however like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar advertising services. This information is not shared with third purposes and you can unsubscribe at any time via phone or email.

**What are your rights?**

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Data Protection Officer who will investigate the matter.

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).

Our Data Protection Officer is Keith Wild. You can contact call him on 01484 400666.
